IN THIS RELEASE:

REQUIREMENTS DOC:

- Added Terminology section
- Updated "scope" to include simple timeline/milestones
- 
SPECIFICATIONS DOC:

- Add user story


APPLICATION:
- Gallery Activity loads images from the phone gallery and displays them
- Folder of stock photos has been added to repo, but not yet added to application
- Not implemented, but majority of research for loading camera has been done

TEST PLAN:

Feature: User Interface
Test: Click on all implemented buttons
Pass: Able to click through to each implemented activity, and return to previous activities
Fail: Any non-implemented button does not work. Document which these are and what occurs.

Feature: Loading photographs from gallery
Test: Load .png from any folder
Pass: Photo loads and is displayed in activity
Fail: Cannot find image, or image does not display

Feature: Loading photographs from gallery
Test: Load .jpeg from any folder
Pass: Photo loads and is displayed in activity
Fail: Cannot find image, or image does not display

Feature: Loading photos from gallery
Test: Load .gif
Pass: Image not found, if image id found, will not load
Fail: Attempts to load image.

Feature: Load photos from dropBox instead of 
Test: Load from dropBox
Pass: find image and is processed by app
Fail: Does not find image and load it.

